Uh, some voice at the
back is want us to try the toe tofu. The
stinking tofu. We have a lot of cows.
Yeah. Ah, they stink and it it remembers
me a little bit.
[Music]
Okay. All right. Let's go. Let's go,
Michael. Let's go.
[Music]
Put it
Michael magic. You see all the things
that we saw downstairs, we brought it
all up and it's incredible. Great.
Great. And now we have to try to mash it
with your great wines. I can describe
couple of the the dishes for you. Wet
spring roll. Ah, okay. It's not the
spring roll you fry. Yeah. Yeah. It's
not the fried. It's called is like to
wet.
[Music]
called the bursting squid duck blood
with stinky tofu. But it's actually very
delicious. Now, this is very special
today. It's called abalone instant
noodle. This is shaolong bao, the local
street food. Shaolong bao, oyster
omelette, Taiwanese style. Okay. Uh this
is a very standard chicken. The most
famous
loab. The company is called. It's called
mustache chain and a fried smelly tofu.
Stinking tofu. Oh, let's try it.
Fantastic. I forgot to introduce who you
are. So,
well,
foreign.
Okay.
Fore caretaker.
[Music]
Sorry, I was just explaining who you
are, but I actually have a really quick
question. uh you were actually involved
in the creation of the the the the
system the the grand crew and the system
of Austria. Can you explain a little bit
to fans because it's very interesting
why there's no grand crew in Austria now
yet? Well, you see when it comes uh to
classifications
uh it is a quite complicated uh history
uh to to to that and a complicated
story. Um but to break it down, you
know, for the essences, um why do we
need a classification? It's very simple.
Looking to single vineyards in Austria,
we talking about 5,000 single vineyards.
Wow. 5,000. Not even we in Austria know
all these names. Okay. So, impossible.
Yeah.
Now what our friends in France
discovered very early is that a
classification helps us uh in the
communication uh of a specific quality
category.
The advantage of a classification system
is that it's easier to communicate a
category of wine than the specific
vineyards that are included actually in
this category. Oh, okay. I got it. You
see, of course. So when you are
communicating you know that okay this
wine is now a premier crew or a crew
then you don't even need to know the
name of the vineyard and you can already
communicate the quality level. Okay. So
it's a quality level communication with
the with the wine lover and also a
guarantee for Exactly. And the
interesting story is that Austria
nowadays is the first country outside of
France with a legal classification
system. That's very important. It's the
first country outside of France with a
legal classification
system
started with you. Starting with the work
of the association
of so the WTW wine makers. Okay. So it's
the traditional wine makers of Austria.
Okay. Um OTW and uh this association was
founded more than 30 years ago and this
association concentrated on the
development of a classification system.
Currently I am the president of
president of this association and uh I
am still very much involved actually
know in the details of this
classification process and so on.
[Music]
Okay, Michael, can you explain to um the
wine lovers and the fans what which wine
is this? Well, uh this is now uh the
domain goblesburg canal Brunoina.
Brunoina is the most fashionable and the
widest planted white wine grape variety
in Austria. And uh the Campal Vina is a
a regional expression of the Camp
Valley. Okay. So it's a it's a wine that
in in in our culture we enjoy on a daily
basis. Okay. So it's a it's a wine that
we enjoy with the the cold suppersh in
the families. Um, it's also a wine that
we enjoy with watching TV, playing
cards, meeting friends. Even in
summertime, we're doing a spritz. Do you
know what a spritz is? No. Uh, in
summertime when it's hot, you know, we
try to drink a little bit more. Okay.
Yeah. Uh, and therefore we make half
wine, half soda. Oh. To make a beverage
with low alcohol. So like four or five
alcohol. Okay. which is very refreshing,
you know, it's very animating, you know,
to drink. Uh, and it's not and you can
drink quite a lot of it, you know. It's
like beer. So, with
wine, uh, we have because during summer
it's very hot. So, we on a c or maybe
like a barbecue and it's very good.
[Music]
All right, let's Well, first let's try
this. How's that? The wet spring rope.
Um, and you you score out of uh 0 to 10.
Oh, 0 to 10. Yeah. You give the matching
score
the volume is perfect, but I mean at
least like an eight. Yeah, I would
definitely say an eight. Now we try with
Zigel. How's that? Okay. Can you explain
to our fans um what great variet is?
Swiggle is a a grape variety, the widest
planted red wine grape variety in
Austria and it originates from the Pon
Noir family. In the 19th century, uh a
child of pinonoir came to Austria and
together with an other autoton grape
variety, Blau Frankish uh the crossing
was made and uh the result was this
grape variety and it's a fantastic grape
variety because it's very universal in
its use. You know, you can make
fantastic regional expressions. If you
have a really good vineyard, old wines,
you can make a great reserve wine as
well.
is saying.
[Music]
Okay. Okay. Let's try if matches this.
Let's let's try it.
Honestly, not that you cannot do it, but
in that case, I'm preferring actually,
you know, the the white wine for the
is a grunell leader. Grunov is how
what's the score you'll give five six
five to six maybe
uh what you want you choose anything you
want well uh we can do maybe the easy
things first easy yeah what do you think
of this this
[Music]
okay well for me very clear uh that's
all goes definitely here to the white
side exactly if you have the score how
much
at least nine Because everything that is
connected to sushi, raw fish and so on,
uh you know, you need a delicate wine.
You you you don't need an offensive wine
with a lot of oak. Okay? So, you rather
need, you know, the delicateness. Um you
see, this wine has a a a nice and decent
aroma, but it's not offensive. I agree.
Nine. And the red maybe about the same
as last one.
Yeah. Okay. Next one. I think we're
going to to the specialtity that we have
in front of you. This So that looks
really delicious. This is really cool
and really and really special.
So, cheers. Cheers. Let's try
[Music]
it. In an emergency, the white wine will
do. But I think I think that you know
with the with the muscle that's it's
much much better you know with the um
with with the uh with the swig. Yeah.
And and because of the sauce too. It's a
little soy sauce. Because of the sauce.
Yeah. Um and and and also you know a a
slight bitterness you know that comes
through which is matched actually by the
wine.
[Music]
actually ziggo if we can you can tell um
you know our fans what is the style of
ziggo uh the style of as parent is or
let's say the grandmother is ponoir um
so it's a light and elegant style um it
it it's a it's a wine that has a decent
fruit aroma um but it also has a little
bit of a spicy note with it I agree so
yeah sweet cheese
Okay. Shall we do one thing maybe? Uh
what we can do more quickly is the
things that we also have in Austria.
Ah so this is something that we can
already you know point out. Ah that's
you know you see you know we are
starting maybe here with a dish yes of
course that somehow you know is very
similar you know to one of the most
famous dishes in Austria. Yes the
venitle
schnitle the
[Music]
famous try. So uh the the venitle of
course is not based on on uh it's not
not not based on on chicken but it's
it's based in ve you know in Austria
however you know the texture is is the
same in
Austria this is the
choice very simple
[Music]
What we also have in Austria of course
liver Austria uh is uh still today is a
nosetotail eating country. Ah same as
us. Yeah. So that's a that's an easy
choice. This is so good. Really? What's
the choice? Try. Okay. You will see.
There's no question.
Ah, no question. Finally.
Yeah. This one, right? So, so far it's
only one point. No. So far it's all
white. No. Except this is the first
time. Well, yeah. Yeah. But actually,
you see you you see uh for this dish.
No. Roasted roasted liver. Yeah. You
don't want actually a deep, you know, a
deep colored intensive, you know, red
wine. Okay. It's also a delicate dish,
you know. I mean, it it it has, you
know, it has it has the, you know, the
the tenants. It has the texture, you
know, but still it's delicate, you know.
Also like pinonoir would go very well
with that. Yeah. But swag is a fantastic
choice. I think spigo is better than
penino because spigo has the
spices little spiciness and then this is
this is what you need actually for Yes.
[Music]
Exactly. Some voice at the
back is want us to try the tofu. The
stinking tofu
tofu and then
Let's try it. So, let's see. So, you you
you hardly can shock Austrians, you
know, so cuz we used, you know, to all
kinds of fancy things.
A little spicy. A little spicy.
This will be interesting.
I have my favorite. Okay. This is a
tough one. Yeah, I have mine. I have
mine.
And you can say yours and I can say
mine. And we don't have to agree with
each other. I think that both in a way
works somehow.
But I have a slight preference actually
for the white. Really? For me is the
red. For you is the red. Yeah. Yeah.
Yeah. The Chinese herb in here and the
smelly tofu. The smelly side of it. Mhm.
And this vigo. The gy in this vigo.
[Music]
gaming. That's I I love it. But the
white is also very good. It's, you know,
I think
that what counts for the red wine, you
know, is is this spicy aroma. Mhm.
In general, I think that tofu in general
is a little bit more on the white wine
side. All right. Yeah. Um because it's
delicate, you know, it has this texture.
Yes. Um which is also supported by the
acidity. That's right. That's right.
Mhm. And uh but I think as I said, you
know, it's it's a tough one. So you I
think in a way, you know, can you can
use both both.
Maybe it's because how they cook it. Now
we tried the same tofu but fried. How's
that? Very good. Looks delicious.
M. Oh, it's good. I like the stingy tofu
both. But I like when it's steamed, it's
more stinky. And when it's fried is
because of the fried, it's less stinky.
You know, I'm I'm I'm coming from the
alpine areas. No, we have in the Alps,
we have a lot of cows. Yeah. Ah, they
stink. And it it remembers me.
Let's try it. This is called the the
bursting squid. Oh, I know why. It's
cucumber and it's um I don't know what's
inside. You try. It looks delicious. It
looks delicious, but it looks also
difficult. And also maybe a little
sauce. I give you a little bit on top.
So, because that's that's always the
sauce is always the most important
thing.
Yes. I agree. when it when it comes to
food matching. Yeah. You know, sauce is
the most important thing, you know, to
look at because the sauce is basically
the basement, you know, for the matching
food and wine.
M
okay. It's difficult.
Difficult.
[Music]
You know what is the difficult thing?
Yeah.
Sauce. Ah.
Okay. Sauce. The sauce has sweetness.
Ah, okay. So, the sauce has sweetness.
The texture is fine. Okay. That works
very well. But the sauce is sweet. Okay.
So, I think we can exclude I think the
red one. Okay. Yes, I agree. Honjo.
How's the red? Yeah. Let's try this.
Yes. It's a little better. I think it's
better. Yeah. But it's not perfect.
Yeah. So like seven. No. But why is not
perfect? So we would say it's six. I
would say it's 67. Maybe 67. Yeah. Now I
want you to try something that's very
similar. It's oyster omelette. It's also
sweet and it's also seafood. Wow. This
is like so much oyster.
Oh, it's oy it's a oyster concentration.
Yeah, I know. Look at that. Here, let me
get you this omelette.
Again, we have a little bit of sweet
element. I think it's again a little bit
more towards the right. Yes. Yes, I
agree.
[Music]
Lastly, I love
this. We call it the mustache chain.
It's called Formosa Chang because Forosa
is Taiwan, but actually the name in
Chinese in Mandarin is called means
mustache and his last name is Chen.
I don't know what you think, William,
but
I think it's okay with this VGO. It's
okay. I
like probably it's a dish that needs a
little bit more body and a little bit
more concentration.
Voila. But maybe I think it's okay.
Something that's stronger red. I think
that this is a dish that probably needs,
you know, a little bit more
concentration, a little bit more
expression.
[Music]
Okay. Okay.
Okay.
[Music]
Real. Okay.
What's Right. Yeah.
[Applause]
Thank you, Michael, for coming. Uh,
thank you for this great experience. You
know, night market is something, you
know, it's incredible. It's something
it's one of a kind. It's one of a kind.
You might think of opening a night
market in Australia. Yeah, we
definitely All
[Music]
right. Cheers. Cheers. Cheers. Cheers.
Cheers.
[Music]